William Hobart Royce Papers
William Hobart Royce Papers
- Printed material
  - Brandes, Louis de (Royce catalog number: R2225) (Box 10)
  - Brasbeau, J. (Box 10)
  - Brasillach, Robert (Box 10)
  - Breillat, Pierre (Box 10)
  - Bridges, William (Box 10)
  - Brion, Marcel (Box 10)
  - Brisson, Adolphe (Box 10)
  - Britt, George (Box 11)
  - Brooks, Jerome (Royce catalog number: R2246) (Box 11)
  - Brooks, Obed (Box 11)
  - Brooks, Philip (Box 11)
  - Brousson, Jean-Jacques (Box 11)
  - Brown, John L. (Royce catalog number: S3784A) (Box 11)
  - Browne, Junius Henri (Royce catalog number: R2254, R2255) (Box 11)
  - Brun, Charles-A (Box 11)
  - Bruneau, Charles (Box 11)
  - Brunet-Houard (Box 11)
  - Brunetiere, Ferdinand (Royce catalog number: R2261, 2265) (Box 11)
  - Brunot, Henriette (Box 11)
  - Bruyr, José (Royce catalog number: R2270) (Box 11)
  - Burns, Robert (Box 11)
  - Burton, Richard (Box 11)
  - Cabanès, Auguste (Royce catalog number: R3003) (Box 11)
  - Callcis, Roger (Box 11)
  - Caillet, Gérard (Box 11)
  - Cain, Julien (Box 11)
  - Campbell, Helen (Box 11)
  - Cantagrel, Roger (Box 11)
  - Canteleu, Comte Le Couteulx de (Box 11)
  - Carbonelle, Henri (Box 11)
  - Carité, Maurice (Box 11)
  - Carli, Decio (Box 11)
  - Caro, E. (Box 11)
  - Cather, Willa (Box 11)
  - Caussy, Fernand (Box 11)
  - Cazenove, Marcel (Box 11)
  - Carzin, Paul (Box 11)
  - Céard, Henry (Box 11)
  - Cendrars, Blaise (Box 11)
  - Cestre, Charles (Box 12)
  - Champfleury (Royce catalog number: R2336) (Box 12)
  - Chamson, André (Box 12)
  - Chancerel, André (Box 12)
  - Chapelan, Maurice (Box 12)
  - Charensol (Royce catalog number: R2347) (Box 12)
  - Charles-Brun, E. (Box 12)
  - Charles, Etienne (Box 12)
  - Charlier, Gustave (Box 12)
  - Charnace, D. De (Box 12)
  - Chastain, André-Henry (Royce catalog number: R2352) (Box 12)
  - Chavance, René (Box 12)
  - Chercheur, Le (Royce catalog number: R2357, R2358) (Box 12)
  - Chevaier, Denys (Box 12)
  - Chevassu, Francis (Royce catalog number: R2361) (Box 12)
  - Chew, Samuel C. (Royce catalog number: R2362) (Box 12)
  - Chiesa, Lorenzo dalla (Box 12)
  - Chonez, Claudine (Box 12)
  - Cladel, Judith (Box 12)
  - Claretié, Jules (Box 12)
  - Clark, Lee (Box 12)
  - Clerk, Charles (Box 12)
  - Clouard, Henri (Box 12)
  - Coblentz, Stanton A. (Royce catalog number: R2395) (Box 12)
  - Cohn, Adolphe (Royce catalog number: R2397) (Box 12)
  - Cohen, Gustave (Box 12)
  - Cohen, Rubin (Box 12)
  - Coiplet, Robert (Box 12)
  - Colette (Box 12)
  - Collins, James H. (Royce catalog number: R2398) (Box 12)
  - Collins, Wilkie (Box 12)
  - Colombier, Pierre de (Box 12)
  - Colt de Wolf, Bradford (Royce catalog number: R2402) (Box 12)
  - Comité du "Balzac" de Rodin (Box 12)
  - Conner, J. Wayne (Box 12)
  - Cook, Keningale (Royce catalog number: R2408, R2409) (Box 12)
  - Coppin, Joseph (Royce catalog number: R2410) (Box 13)
  - Coquiot, Gustave (Box 13)
  - Crawfurd, Oswald (Royce catalog number: R2418) (Box 13)
  - Crepet, Jacques (Royce catalog number: R2419) (Box 13)
  - Couvreur, Jean (Box 13)
  - Courville, Georges (Box 13)
  - Crévecoeur (Box 13)
  - Croce, Benedetto (Royce catalog number: R2421) (Box 13)
  - Crowley, Aleister (Royce catalog number: R358) (Box 13)
  - Croze, J.-L. (Box 13)
  - Curnousky, M. (Box 13)
  - Cournousky, M., and Bienstock, J.-W. (Royce catalog number: R2423) (Box 13)
  - Curtius, Ernst-Robert (Royce catalog number: R2426) (Box 13)
  - Curts, Jack (Box 13)
  - Dacier, Ralph (Royce catalog number: R2432) (Box 13)
  - Dargan, E. Preston (Royce catalog number: R2438) (Box 13)
  - Dark, Sidney (Box 13)
  - Daudet, Léon (Box 13)
  - Daudon, René (Box 13)
  - Darignon, Henri (Box 13)
  - Davis, Bob (Box 13)
  - Day, F. Holland (Royce catalog number: R2456) (Box 13)
  - Deanville, May (Box 13)
  - De Casseres, Benjamin (Royce catalog number: R2460) (Box 13)
  - Deauville, Max (Royce catalog number: R2457) (Box 13)
  - Delacour, André (Box 13)
  - Delécluze, Étienne-Jean (Box 13)
  - Delon, Georges (Box 13)
  - Delorme, Hugnez (Box 13)
  - Demeure, Fernand (Box 13)
  - Demilly, Adolphe (Box 13)
  - Dermée, Paul (Box 14)
  - Deroger, Michelle (Box 14)
  - Derys, Gaston (Royce catalog number: R2475) (Box 14)
  - Desanti, Dominique (Box 14)
  - Desbordes-Valmore, Marceline (Royce catalog number: R2476) (Box 14)
  - Descaves, Lucien (Box 14)
  - Descaves, Pierre (Box 14)
  - Des Granges, Charles-Marie (Royce catalog number: R2490) (Box 14)
  - Després, René (Box 14)
  - Des Prugnes, Robert (Box 14)
  - Dethez, Albert (Box 14)
  - Dieuaide, A. (Royce catalog number: R2941) (Box 14)
  - Dodd, Lee Wilson (Box 14)
  - Doumic, René (Royce catalog number: R2507) (Box 14)
  - Drake, William A. (Box 14)
  - Dredd, Firmin (Royce catalog number: R2512) (Box 14)
  - Drion, Huib (Box 14)
  - Drumont, Édouard (Box 14)
  - Dubalek, Felix (Box 14)
  - Duberry, Henri (Box 14)
  - Dubay, Pierre (Royce catalog number: R2518) (Box 14)
  - Dupuy, Aimé (Box 14)
  - Durtal (Box 14)
  - Dutacq, Jean (Box 14)
  - Dyck, Richard (Box 14)
  - Eaton, Walter Prichard (Box 14)
  - Edgett, E.F. (Box 14)
  - Edmond, Paul (Royce catalog number: R2947) (Box 14)
  - Erio, Paul (Box 14)
  - Elst, J. Van der (Box 14)
  - Emmanuel, Pierre (Box 14)
  - Erceville, S.M. De (Box 15)
  - Erskine, John (Royce catalog number: S4174) (Box 15)
  - Escholier, Raymond (Box 15)
  - Espiau, Marcel (Box 15)
  - Espina, Antonio (Box 15)
  - Estrangin, Guy F. (Box 15)
  - Etienne, Louis (Royce catalog number: R2546) (Box 15)
  - Evans, David Owen (Box 15)
  - Fadiman, Clifton P. (Box 15)
  - Faguet, Émile (Royce catalog number: R2553, R2560) (Box 15)
  - Fairman, Milton (Box 15)
  - Falconer, W.L. (Royce catalog number: R2564) (Box 15)
  - Fallois, Bernard de (Box 15)
  - Farrell, James J. (Box 15)
  - Faure, Gabriel (Royce catalog number: R2566) (Box 15)
  - Faure-Bignet, J.-N. (Box 15)
  - Ferdar, Émile (Box 15)
  - Fernandez, Ramón (Royce catalog number: R2572) (Box 15)
  - Ferran, Anré (Box 15)
  - Ferry, Gabriel (Royce catalog number: R2577, R2580, R2581, R2582, R2583, R2587, R2589, R2591) (Box 15)
  - Fess, Gilbert Malcolm [empty envelop] (Box 15)
  - Fiessinger, Ch. (Box 15)
  - Fiéret, A. (Box 15)
  - Finamore, Michele (Box 15)
  - Fiske, John Safford (Royce catalog number: R2603) (Box 15)
  - Fisher, W.E. Garrett (Royce catalog number: R2606) (Box 15)
  - Fitzgerald, Ellen (Royce catalog number: R2604) (Box 15)
  - Flaneur, Le (Box 15)
  - Flandreysy, Jeanne de (Box 15)
  - Flat, Paul (Royce catalog number: R2616) (Box 15)
  - Flers, Robert de (Box 15)
  - Fleurs, Robert de (Royce catalog number: R2619) (Box 15)
  - Flood, Renée (Box 15)
  - Florence, Jean (Box 15)
  - Foley, Charles (Box 15)
  - Fontenoy, Henri (Box 15)
  - Forest, H.U. (Box 15)
  - Forman, Henry James (Box 15)
  - Fouqueure, André (Box 16)
  - Franc-Nohain (Box 16)
  - Frank, Nino (Box 16)
  - Freeman, David (Box 16)
  - Fréteval, Jean (Box 16)
  - Frollo, Jean (Box 16)
  - Frye, Prosser Hall (Box 16)
  - Furman, Alfred Antoine (Royce catalog number: R552) (Box 16)
  - Furne, Charles (Box 16)
  - Gaffarel, Paul (Box 16)
  - Galantière, Lewis (Royce catalog number: R2655) (Box 16)
  - Gallotti, Jean (Box 16)
  - Gandon, Yves (Box 16)
  - Gannett, Lewis (Box 16)
  - Gastaldi, Santiago, 4 folders (Box 16)
  - Gastaldi, Santiago, 5 folders (Box 17)
  - Gaubert, Ernest (Box 17)
  - Gauchez, Maurice (Box 17)
  - Gautier (Box 18)
  - Gauss, Christian (Box 18)
  - Gauthier, Jacques (Box 18)
  - Gautier, Théophile (Royce catalog number: R2680) (Box 18)
  - George, Albert J., and Wells, Lester G. (Box 18)
  - George, W.L. (Royce catalog number: R2700) (Box 18)
  - George (Box 18)
  - Getteman, Auguste (Royce catalog number: R2704) (Box 18)
  - Gibb, Margaret Murray (Box 18)
  - Gide, Andre (Box 18)
  - Gilbert, Eugène (Box 18)
  - Gill, And. (Box 18)
  - Ginisty, Paul (Royce catalog number: R2715, R2716) (Box 18)
  - Girard, Georges (Box 18)
  - Girard, Maxime (Royce catalog number: R2721) (Box 18)
  - Giron, Roger (Box 18)
  - Giusso, Lorenzo (Box 18)
  - Givens, Mary L. (Box 18)
  - Gleadell, W.H. (Royce catalog number: R2726) (Box 18)
  - Goldschneider, Cécile (Box 18)
  - Gorki, Maxime (Royce catalog number: R2734) (Box 18)
  - Gorman, Herbert (Box 18)
  - Gosset, Léon (Royce catalog number: R2735) (Box 18)
  - Got, R.; Guth, Paul; Hoog, Armand; Loize, Jean; Metzel, Boris; Nadeau, Maurice; Picard, Gaston; Picon, Gaëtan; Sigeaux, Gilbert (Box 18)
  - Gouthier, Henri (Box 18)
  - Goulard, Roger (Box 18)
  - Gould, Charles (Box 18)
  - Gourmont, J. de (Royce catalog number: R2738) (Box 18)
  - Gozlan, Léon (Royce catalog number: R2746) (Box 18)
  - Grammont, Jean (Box 18)
  - Grandmaison, Louis de (Royce catalog number: R2750) (Box 18)
  - Granzotto, Gianni (Box 18)
  - Grappe, Georges (Box 18)
  - Grasser, Jean-Laurent (Box 19)
  - Grasset, Bernard (Box 19)
  - Gregh, Fernand (Royce catalog number: R2755) (Box 19)
  - Grenier, Jean (Box 19)
  - Grippe-Soleil (Box 19)
  - Groc, Léon (Box 19)
  - Guérard, Albert (Box 19)
  - Guiard, Marcel (Box 19)
  - Guillemin, Henri (Box 19)
  - Guinand, Jean (Box 19)
  - Guyon, Bernard (Box 19)
  - Guyot, Charly (Box 19)
  - Guyot, Yves (Box 19)
  - Haas, J. (Box 19)
  - Hake, Thomas St.E. (Royce catalog number: R2775) (Box 19)
  - Hale, Philip (Box 19)
  - Hanlon, Louis (Box 19)
  - Hancock, Albert Elmer (Royce catalog number: R2780) (Box 19)
  - Hannigan, D.F. "In My Study" (Box 19)
  - Hanotaux, Gabriel (Royce catalog number: R2781, R2783) (Box 19)
  - Hanotaux, Gabriel (Oversize 2)
  - Hansen, Harry (Royce catalog number: R2784) (Box 19)
  - Harper, George McLean (Royce catalog number: R2785) (Box 19)
  - Harry, Myriam (Royce catalog number: R2787) (Box 19)
  - Hastings, Walter Scott (Royce catalog number: R2788, R2789, R2790) (Box 19)
  - Hauser, Fernand (Box 19)
  - Hazzlit, Henry (Box 20)
  - [Heartman, Charles] (Box 20)
  - Helm, W.H. (Royce catalog number: R2805, R2811) (Box 20)
  - Henley, William Ernest (Royce catalog number: R2812) (Box 20)
  - Hennion, Horace (Royce catalog number: S4639E, S4639F, S4639G, S4639H), 5 folders (Box 20)
  - Hennion, Horace, 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Henriot, Émile (Royce catalog number: R2816, R2818, R2823, R2824, R2825, R2826, R2827), 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Henriquez, Jack [or Jaques; pseud. Ki Wist] (Box 21)
  - Hercourt, Jean (Box 21)
  - Hériat, Philippe (Box 22)
  - Herman, Arthur (Box 22)
  - Hermant, Abel (Royce catalog number: R2829) (Box 22)
  - Héros. Eugène (Box 22)
  - Hervey, Charles (Royce catalog number: R2833) (Box 22)
  - Heydt, Herman A. (Box 22)
  - Hickok, Guy (Box 22)
  - Hillard, Katherine (Box 22)
  - Hofmannsthal, Hugo von (Royce catalog number: R2837) (Box 22)
  - Holden, Edward S. (Royce catalog number: R2841) (Box 22)
  - Hoog, Armand (Royce catalog number: S4671A) (Box 22)
  - Hopkins, Frederick (Box 22)
  - Hopkins, Tighe (Box 22)
  - Hosotte, Louis (Royce catalog number: R2844) (Box 22)
  - Hough, Henry Beetle (Box 22)
  - Hourdin, Georges (Box 22)
  - Huard, Frances Wilson (Royce catalog number: R2850) (Box 22)
  - Huard, Charles (Box 22)
  - Huart, Marcel (Box 22)
  - Hubbard, Elbert (Box 22)
  - Hubac, Pierre (Royce catalog number: R2852, 2853) (Box 22)
  - Hugalde, Isabel Pernas (Box 22)
  - Hugault, Henry (Box 22)
  - Hughes, Randolph (Box 22)
  - Hugo, Victor (Royce catalog number: R2858) (Box 22)
  - Hunter, Richard S. (Royce catalog number: R2864) (Box 22)
  - Huret, Jules (Royce catalog number: R2465) (Box 22)
  - Ibánaz, Vicente Blasco (Royce catalog number: R2868) (Box 22)
  - Jackson, Joseph F. (Royce catalog number: R3063) (Box 22)
  - Jaloux, Edmond (Box 22)
  - James, Henry (Royce catalog number: R3067, R3068, R3070) (Box 22)
  - Jammes, Francis (Box 22)
  - Janin, Jules (Royce catalog number: R3074) (Box 22)
  - Jarblum, Irène (Box 22)
  - Jarry, Paul (Royce catalog number: R3090, R3091) (Box 23)
  - Jean-Aubry, G. (Box 23)
  - Johnson, Virginia W. (Royce catalog number: R3096) (Box 23)
  - Johnston, Alva (Box 23)
  - Johnston, Charles, and Spencer, C. (Royce catalog number: R3097) (Box 23)
  - Jollivet, Simone (Box 23)
  - Jones, Ernest (Box 23)
  - Josephson, Matthew (Box 23)
  - Jouin, Henry (Royce catalog number: R3100) (Box 23)
  - Jules-Bois, H.A. (Box 23)
  - Kahn, Gustave (Royce catalog number: R3107, R3108) (Box 23)
  - Kahan-Rabecq, M.M. (Box 23)
  - Kemp, Robert (Box 23)
  - Keany, George (Box 23)
  - Kent, Philip (Royce catalog number: R3111, R3112) (Box 23)
  - Kihlman, Herman (Box 23)
  - Kingdon, Frank (Box 23)
  - Kleinmichel, Comtesse Marie (Royce catalog number: R3115) (Box 23)
  - Knight, Joseph (Royce catalog number: R3117) (Box 23)
  - Kronenberger, Louis (Box 23)
  - Krutch, Joseph Wood (Box 23)
  - Kündig, H. (Royce catalog number: R3121) (Box 23)
  - Kuza, W. (Box 23)
  - Labracherie, Pierre (Box 23)
  - Lacoste, Josette (Box 23)
  - Ladvocat (Royce catalog number: R3134) (Box 23)
  - Lafleur, Paul F. (Royce catalog number: R3136) (Box 23)
  - La Jeunesse, Ernest (Box 23)
  - Lalo, Charles (Box 23)
  - Lalou, René (Box 24)
  - Lancaster, H.C. (Box 24)
  - Lang, Georges-Emmanuel (Royce catalog number: R3144) (Box 24)
  - Langers. Pierre (Box 24)
  - Langley, Ernest F. (Box 24)
  - Lannes, Roger (Box 24)
  - Lanson, Gustave (Royce catalog number: R3146) (Box 24)
  - Lapaire, Huguez (Box 24)
  - Lapie, P.O. (Box 24)
  - Laprade, Jacques de (Box 24)
  - Larguier, Leo (Box 24)
  - La Sablière, François de (Box 24)
  - Latourette, Louis (Royce catalog number: R3159) (Box 24)
  - Laugel, A. (Royce catalog number: R3161, R3162) (Box 24)
  - Lavadeur, Patrick (Box 24)
  - Lavedan, Pierre (Royce catalog number: R3163) (Box 24)
  - Lavrischeff, Eloise (Box 24)
  - Leblond, Marius-Ary (Box 24)
  - Lebouc, Jules (Box 24)
  - Le Breton, André (Royce catalog number: R3168, R3169) (Box 24)
  - Lecigne, C. (Royce catalog number: R822) (Box 24)
  - Le Coq, M.-J. (Box 24)
  - Lécyer, Raymond (Box 24)
  - Ledent, Roger (Box 24)
  - Ledru-Rollin (Box 24)
  - Lefèvre, Frédéric (Royce catalog number: R3181) (Box 24)
  - Le Fouineur (Box 24)
  - Lefranc, Jean (Royce catalog number: R3184) (Box 24)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (Box 24)
  - Le Gentil, René (Box 24)
  - Léger, Charles (Royce catalog number: R3187, R3188, R3190) (Box 25)
  - Lemonnier, Monique (Box 25)
  - Lenôtre, G. (Royce catalog number: R3198) (Box 25)
  - Lepage, Édouard (Box 25)
  - Lepage, Henry (Royce catalog number: R3200) (Box 25)
  - Lerminier, J.L.E. (Royce catalog number: R3203) (Box 25)
  - Leroy, Louis (Royce catalog number: S4922A) (Box 25)
  - Levaillant, Maurice (Royce catalog number: R3209, R3210, R3211, R3212, R3213, R3214, R3215, R3216, R3217 ) (Box 25)
  - [Levaillant, Maurice?] (L., M.) (Royce catalog number: R3128) (Box 25)
  - Levander, [Hans] (Box 25)
  - Levinson, André (Box 25)
  - Levron, Jacques (Box 25)
  - Lewis, Lloyd (Box 25)
  - Lewys, Georges (Box 25)
  - Lièvre, Pierre (Box 25)
  - Lilly, William Samuel (Royce catalog number: R3225, R3226) (Box 25)
  - Liseur, Le (Box 25)
  - Littlefield, Walter (Royce catalog number: R3230) (Box 25)
  - Lloyd (Box 25)
  - Lœwel, Pierre (Box 25)
  - Loïc, Pierre (Box 25)
  - Loize, Jean (Box 25)
  - Loménie, Louis de (Royce catalog number: R555) (Box 25)
  - London, John o' (Box 25)
  - Lotte, Fernand (Royce catalog number: S4969A) (Box 25)
  - Louÿz, Pierre (Royce catalog number: R3244) (Box 25)
  - Lovenjoul, Charles de (Royce catalog number: R2939) (Box 26)
  - Loving, Pierre (Royce catalog number: R3245) (Box 26)
  - Lowenthal, Marvin (Royce catalog number: S4971) (Box 26)
  - Ludwig, Emil (Royce catalog number: R3251) (Box 26)
  - Lumet, Louis (Royce catalog number: R3252, R3253, R3254) (Box 26)
  - Lurin, Louis (Box 26)
  - Lvouski, Zinovy (Box 26)
  - Lynn, Jacques (Box 26)
  - Mabbott, J.O. (Box 26)
  - Mabie, Hamilton W. (Box 26)
  - MacDonnell, John de Courcy (Royce catalog number: R3264) (Box 26)
  - MacKall, Leonard L. (Box 26)
  - Mabille de Poncheville, A. (Box 26)
  - Madaule, Jacque (Box 26)
  - Malo, Henri (Royce catalog number: R3277, R3278) (Box 26)
  - Mann, Heinrich (Box 26)
  - Manderoy, René (Box 26)
  - Mannoni, Paul (Box 26)
  - Manziarly, Alex de (Box 26)
  - Mapes, Ella Stryker (Royce catalog number: R3283) (Box 26)
  - Márai, Sandor (Royce catalog number: R3284) (Box 26)
  - Marble, Annie Russel (Royce catalog number: R3285) (Box 26)
  - Marcade, Auguste (Box 26)
  - Marceau, Félicien (Box 26)
  - Marès, Roland de (Royce catalog number: R3289) (Box 26)
  - Marie, Aristide (Box 26)
  - Marix, Thérèse (Box 26)
  - Marques, Denis (Box 26)
  - Marsan, Eugène (Box 26)
  - Marsan, Jules (Box 26)
  - Marteau, Jean (Box 26)
  - Martel, Tancrède (Royce catalog number: R3294) (Box 26)
  - Martin, B.E. And C. M. (Royce catalog number: R3295) (Box 26)
  - Martin, Max (Box 26)
  - Martineau, René (Royce catalog number: R3299) (Box 26)
  - Mason, Wildred (Royce catalog number: R3303) (Box 26)
  - Masques, Les (Box 27)
  - Massant, Raymond (Box 27)
  - Massis, Henri (Box 27)
  - Mathiex, Paul (Box 27)
  - Maupassant, Guy de (Box 27)
  - Maurevert, Georges (Box 27)
  - Mauriac, Claude (Box 27)
  - Maurice, Arthur (Box 27)
  - Maurice, Arthur Bartlett (Box 27)
  - Maurois, André I (Box 27)
  - Maurois, André II (Box 27)
  - McAree, J.V. (Box 27)
  - McCausland, Elisabeth (Box 27)
  - McFee, William (Box 27)
  - Meetkerke, C.E. (Box 27)
  - Meillac, Camille (Box 27)
  - Mélesville, M.M. And Duveyrier, C. (Royce catalog number: R933) (Box 27)
  - Melia, Jean (Royce catalog number: R3319) (Box 27)
  - Méré, Charles (Royce catalog number: R3322) (Box 27)
  - Merlant, Joachim (Royce catalog number: R3329) (Box 27)
  - Méryan, Claude (Box 27)
  - Messières, Renè de (Royce catalog number: S5115A) (Box 27)
  - Meylan, Pierre (Royce catalog number: S5118) (Box 27)
  - Michand, Régis (Box 27)
  - Michel, H. (Royce catalog number: R957) (Box 27)
  - Middleton, George (Box 27)
  - Mille, Pierre (Box 28)
  - Mille, Piere, and Flores, Angel (Box 28)
  - Miomandre, Francis de (Royce catalog number: S5142, S5142A) (Box 28)
  - Mirbeau, Octave (Royce catalog number: R954) (Box 28)
  - Mitchell, Clifford (Box 28)
  - Mitton, Fernand (Box 28)
  - Mitty, Jean de (Box 28)
  - Mok, Michel (Box 28)
  - Molles, Marie Devening (Box 28)
  - Molloy, J. Fitzgerald (Royce catalog number: R3353) (Box 28)
  - Monahan, Michael (Royce catalog number: R3354) (Box 28)
  - Mongredien, Georges (Box 28)
  - Monier, R. (Box 28)
  - Mouselet, Charles (Royce catalog number: R3359, R3360) (Box 28)
  - Monsigny (Box 28)
  - Montel, François (Royce catalog number: R3364, R3365, R3368, R3369, R3372, R3378), 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Montzaigle, Paul de (Royce catalog number: R2999) (Box 28)
  - Monval, Jean (Box 28)
  - Moore, George (Box 29)
  - Morand, Paul (Box 29)
  - Morembert, H. De (Box 29)
  - Moreno, E. (Box 29)
  - Morhardt, Mathias (Box 29)
  - Moser, Françoise (Box 29)
  - Moussat, Émile (Box 29)
  - Mousset, Albert (Royce catalog number: R3402) (Box 29)
  - Mousset-Merey, A. (Royce catalog number: R3400) (Box 29)
  - Nairne, Campbell (Box 29)
  - Nels, Jacques (Box 29)
  - Nemésio, Vitorino (Box 29)
  - Nicholls, N. and W. (Box 29)
  - Nilsson-Ehle, Hans (Box 29)
  - Nordau, Max (Box 29)
  - Norton, G.M. (Royce catalog number: R3478) (Box 29)
  - Nozière, Fernand (Box 29)
  - O'Brien, Edward J. (Box 29)
  - Oppenheim, Ralph (Royce catalog number: R3486) (Box 29)
  - Orr, Lyndon (Royce catalog number: R3487, R3488) (Box 29)
  - Orthys, Fred (Box 29)
  - Oswald, Marianne (Royce catalog number: S5239A) (Box 29)
  - Padroso, Silvio (Box 29)
  - Pailleron, Marie-Louise (Box 29)
  - Palencia, Ceferino (Box 29)
  - Palfrey, Thomas R. (Box 29)
  - Palme, Sven Ulric (Box 29)
  - Parker, D.C. (Royce catalog number: R3504) (Box 29)
  - Parrot, Louis (Box 29)
  - Parsons, George Frederic (Royce catalog number: R3505) (Box 29)
  - Pascal, Félicien (Royce catalog number: R3516, R3517) (Box 29)
  - Patin, Lacques (Royce catalog number: R3522, R3523, R3524, R3525) (Box 29)
  - Paul-Bousquet, Marina (Box 29)
  - Pechegut, C. (Box 29)
  - Peck, Harry Thurston (Royce catalog number: R3529) (Box 29)
  - Pécuchet, Aloysius (Box 29)
  - Péguy. Charles (Box 29)
  - Pellissier, Georges (Royce catalog number: R3533) (Box 29)
  - Pereira, Consiglieri sa (Box 29)
  - Pereire, Alfred (Box 29)
  - Pérès, J. (Royce catalog number: R3536) (Box 29)
  - Perry, T.S. (Royce catalog number: R3540) (Box 29)
  - Petit, Henri (Box 29)
  - Petit, Jean (Box 29)
  - Petitot, J. (Box 29)
  - Pesti, Naplö (Box 29)
  - Peyre, Henri (Box 29)
  - Peytel, Adrien (Box 29)
  - Piatier, Jacqueline (Box 29)
  - Picard, Gaston (Royce catalog number: R3549, R3550, R3552) (Box 29)
  - Pick, Robert (Box 29)
  - Pillement, Georges (Box 29)
  - Piérard, Louis (Box 29)
  - Pierra (Box 29)
  - Pierre, André (Box 30)
  - Pierre, Victor (Royce catalog number: R3558) (Box 30)
  - Pierrefeu, Jean de (Royce catalog number: R3559) (Box 30)
  - Pilon, Edmond (Royce catalog number: R3561) (Box 30)
  - Pinson, Paul et al. (Royce catalog number: R2944) (Box 30)
  - Pinthus, Kurt (Royce catalog number: R3566) (Box 30)
  - Pinvert, Lucien (Royce catalog number: R3567) (Box 30)
  - Pijotat, Raymond (Box 30)
  - Pitrou, Robert (Box 30)
  - Place, Joseph (Royce catalog number: R3574, R3575, R3576, R3577, R3578) (Box 30)
  - Placido e Silva, de (Box 30)
  - Plauzoles, Joseph (Box 30)
  - Pogany, Joseph (Box 30)
  - Pohl, Gerhart (Box 30)
  - Poitou, Eugène (Royce catalog number: R3583) (Box 30)
  - Pommier, Jean (Box 30)
  - Poncheville, André M. De (Box 30)
  - Pontmartin, Armand de (Box 31)
  - Porché, Francois (Box 30)
  - Poulet, Georges (Box 30)
  - Pourchet, Maurice (Box 30)
  - Preston, Ethel (Box 30)
  - Prévost, Marcel (Box 30)
  - Prinet, Gaston (Box 30)
  - Prior, Henry (Royce catalog number: R3600, R3601, R3602), 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Prist, Paul (Box 30)
  - Prod'homme, J.-G. (Box 30)
  - Puel, Désiré (Box 31)
  - Radziwill, Princesse Catherine (Royce catalog number: R3615, R3616, R3617) (Box 31)
  - Rageot, Gaston (Royce catalog number: R3620) (Box 31)
  - Ramband, Henri (Box 31)
  - Randall, A.W.G. (Box 31)
  - Ravon, Georges (Box 31)
  - Reck-Malleczwen (Royce catalog number: R3627) (Box 31)
  - Reclus, Maurice (Box 31)
  - Regard, Maurice (Box 31)
  - Régis, Roger (Box 31)
  - Regnier, Henri de (Box 31)
  - Reh, Alfred (Box 31)
  - Renand, Jean-Joseph (Box 31)
  - Reval, Gabrielle (Box 31)
  - Révész, Béla (Box 31)
  - Reymond, Arnold (Box 32)
  - Rhodes, Albert (Royce catalog number: R3637) (Box 32)
  - Richard, Marius (Box 32)
  - Richard, Marius, and Roubier, Jean (Box 32)
  - Rickel, Harry (Royce catalog number: 12959) (Box 32)
  - Riebe, Edgar Carlos (Royce catalog number: R3640) (Box 32)
  - Rigaud, A. (Box 32)
  - Ris, Louis Clément de (Box 32)
  - Risley, R.V. (Royce catalog number: R3642) (Box 32)
  - Robert le Diable (Box 32)
  - Roberts, William (Box 32)
  - Rodocanachi, E. (Royce catalog number: R3654) (Box 32)
  - Rogers, W.G. (Box 32)
  - Rollins, Carl Purington (Box 32)
  - Rolland, Amédée (Royce catalog number: R3655) (Box 32)
  - Romane, Jacques (Box 32)
  - Ronin, Paul (Box 32)
  - Rónai, Paul (Box 32)
  - Rops, Daniel (Box 32)
  - Rosny Ainé, J.H. (Box 32)
  - Rougemont, Édouard de (Royce catalog number: R3660) (Box 32)
  - Rousseaux, André (Box 32)
  - Roussilon, L.E. (Royce catalog number: R3661, R3662) (Box 32)
  - Roux, Marquis de (Box 32)
  - Roy, Claude (Box 32)
  - Royaumont, Louis de (Box 32)
  - Royce, William Hobart (Box 32)
  - Royce, William Hobart, 3 folders (Box 33)
  - Royce, William Hobart (Box 93)
  - Rudwin, Maximilian (Box 33)
  - Sacy, S. De (Box 33)
  - Saint-Cyr, Charles de (Box 33)
  - Saint-Georges, Maurice-André (Box 33)
  - Sainte-Beuve, C.A. (Box 33)
  - Sainte-Croix, Camille de (Box 33)
  - Saintsbury, George (Royce catalog number: R3722) (Box 33)
  - Saldaña, J.M. Fernández (Box 33)
  - Salmon, André (Box 33)
  - Saltus, Edgar (Box 33)